Eh, looks delicious!
Looks delicious.
Wow!
Oh, no.
Oh, oh, oh, a snack?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
They know.
Wait a minute. I'm pretty shocked.
What's this?
Hello, everyone. I'm Flame Tamura of Sakura-zaka 46.
Hello everyone!
Do you know what I'm going to do on Youtube today?
You know what I'm going to do on youtube today?
Yes, that's right! Cooking! Yay!
I would like to challenge a cooking project.
The reason why I decided to do a cooking project this time is because
I thought it would be nice if I could make a lunch box and give it to a certain member.
I decided to take on the challenge of a cooking project.
I've never had someone other than my family eat my lunch before.
I'm very, very, very, very worried about it.
I'm going to do my best in my own way.
I'll do my best!
Okay, then, let's start cooking!
I'll start.
Okay, then.
I'd like to start with the meat and potatoes.
By the way, this is my first try.
Can you do it?
I'll look at a book.
First, cut potatoes into bite-sized pieces.
Cut into bite-sized pieces and soak in water for 5 minutes.
You're seeing it for the first time?
I'll peel them.
I've already washed them in water.
Okay, okay.
I'll just drop them in here.
What made you decide to start cooking?
I don't know... but since I started living alone...
There came a time when I felt I had to do something to survive.
That's why I started cooking.
And I cut it into bite-sized pieces.
I'm not good at this.
Bite-sized? Well, let's cut it once.
How big is it?
Like this?
Let's see.
Oh, it's a little big, isn't it?
I told the crab... oh, I said it.
I said it. I said it.
And cut it.
Cut it in half,
So you cut one, two, three, four, so one, two, three.
See you in the next video.
And then, with the peeler...
There it is! Peeler.
Oh, really, I'm best at peeling carrots.
I was never good at peeling potatoes.
I used to help out at home.
I was good at peeling carrots.
I was good at it.
May I?
Okay.
I'm taking this very seriously. Carrots and carrots.
Okay?
All right.
Maybe one of them is too big.
Oh! Hard!
Hard.
A little smaller is better than a long one
The voice of heaven
About this big?
I don't know.
You mean like this?
It's a bento. It can't be too big.
You know what I mean?
Potatoes!
Wow!
That's good!
And then...
Fry the potatoes, and when the oil is clear, add the onions
Yes! Transparency?
The transparency of the potatoes
Like this
Yes, sir!
Now I see what you mean about transparency.
I love potatoes!
I'll get burnt!
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
I've mixed the ice cream with the kan-ya-kan-ya-kan-ya
It's because you cook them, isn't it!
Oh, okay, I'm so surprised.
I have a weird feeling.
Is it okay?
I didn't know there was so much water in it.
So?
Let it simmer for 10 minutes without stirring. Yes!
Ah! Where's the meat?
I forgot to put the meat in. I did it. We had to fry it together.
This happens sometimes, doesn't it?
But sometimes we eat meat like this.But sometimes meat is eaten like this.
Ta-da! What do you think?
I read that you shouldn't stir the meat too much. I was tempted to stir it, but I did it like this.
Put in a human being. Oh, I didn't project it.
Human input.
It's done! The meat and potatoes are done!
Bee, bee, bee, bee, bee!
Another dish! One more!
Still one more!
Okay, now let's make the vegetable meat rolls!
What?
Prepare the vegetables. Cut the carrots into small pieces.
Cut off the stems of the peas.
Cut the carrots into small pieces.
Ho!
Yo!
Well, it's good if you can eat it once, no matter what
Fine, fine, fine is good
Cook for 1 minute and leave it
Start!
OK, OK, OK
phew!
Koukou.
Recently...
What do you think?
What's going on lately?
Naho...
Lately...
Let's talk about cooking.
Well... what I cook most often is...
Well, it's not cooking.
I often have a potluck at home. It's easy.
It's easy, just cut vegetables and put them in.
but once, when I cooked mackerel with miso, I made it.
Once, when I made mackerel stewed in miso
I made a big mistake
Like grilled mackerel
It was kind of miso...
I guess I'm not very good at cooking food that is stewed
It was difficult.
Now, let's roll it up.
This is absolutely delicious.
Yaay!
Looks delicious.
It looks delicious!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want a little bit of sweetness, so...
Let's see.
I put in a tablespoon of sugar, like a half a tablespoon or something like that.
I don't know, but I'll put it in.
I don't know, but let's put it in.
Oh, no, there's definitely sugar in there.
I should have mixed it in.
With the sauce.
Oh, okay.
Oh!
That looks pretty good.
Ta-da!
Done!
The second item is done!
Here we go!
Oh, I got it!
Okay. Okay, last but not least, I'm going to make a lot of sausages!
I don't know if this is normal, but my family used to eat sausage and egg rolls with mayonnaise!
Is that normal? Now, yes, the tour recently ended.
We're working on our sixth single, which will be released around the time this one comes out.
I wonder if it will be out by the time this is published. Thank you for watching our music videos!
Let's see, the 6th single is, this time, Karin!
The title song, which is centered on Karin Fujii, has been a bit of a long time in the making, but it's still a very good song.
But... but...
I thought it was Karin, as I told Karin.
No, in a really good way, I really wanted to see her as a fan.
I've always wanted to see her as a fan, so I'm very happy to have this opportunity to show it to more people.
I'm looking forward to it.
This real red takoyaki is takoyaki. I used to like red sausage, a lot of sausage, when I was in elementary school.
I used to like a lot of sausages when I was in elementary school. I used to have that image.
I think I've had enough of it. Red takoyaki for special occasions like athletic meets.
Not takoyaki! I think it's not octopus, it's sausage.
This is how it's done, Mr. Tako.
Anyo!
It's good, isn't it?
Bon appétit.
Yes!
It's so, so, so delicious!
As for the omelet, well, I want to make the Tamura family's special omelet.
Yay!
My brother is very strict about omelettes in the Tamura family, and my mom has been making them for me since I was a little girl,
My mom has been making bento boxes for me since I was little, so she would try all kinds of soup stock to make them.I don't know
ohohohohohoho!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait! Oh no!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Well, it's just the first one.
Wait, is that fire?
What, what, what, what happened?
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
What? Why? Turn it down a little bit.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Aah! It's open!
Wait a minute.
It's got a hole in it.
Why?
It's okay.
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
But the size of the hole is bigger than the shoulder.
Last one.
Oh, shit.
Oh!
Oh, here it comes!
Whoa! That's good!
Finally, I got it.
I got it.
Finished!
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
Oh! Oh, yeah!
Yes!
Ta-da!
Fried egg
Okay, now I would like to make the last onigiri!
I will make onigiri with the face of the recipient and my own face on it!
I haven't made onigiri since elementary school.
I'm not sure.
I wonder how big they are?
Maybe it's too small.
Maybe a little more.
To learn how to make onigiri, click on the link in the upper right corner!
I've got a cute face!
Let's serve it up a little more!
I'd like to go give it to him now!
I'm so excited!
Clean-chan, thanks for waiting! You don't know what you're doing.
I don't know what I'm going to do...
I made lunch for you. I wanted you to eat it.
What? Why? Well, I'll put it down for a while. I thought it might be a dessert.
Yes, I made this bento for you, Yoshimi-chan Yes, this is the 6th single
I made this lunch box for Ms. Karin because she is going to play the center role, and I wanted to thank her for her performance, and I also wanted her to have this lunch box to give her more power.
No power? I made everything, really.
It was supposed to take about an hour and a half or two hours, but it took me three hours.
So it's a bento made with love? Yes, look, look. Please open it. It's the first time I've ever had a non-family member open it.
Are you okay?
I want to eat it. I don't know if I'm making the right impression.
I want some. I'd like a drink.
I'm so happy.
Wow, wow, wow. It's so beautiful.
It's like I'm a girl.
Wow.
Hey, hey, hey.
There's definitely someone you want to marry.
Really?
You should really go for it. Think about Kani all the time.
This, this.
This is it.
There's a theme.
The theme of this bento.
Crab and his friends' start over.
Wait a minute.
It's like...
Redo?
It's not really about a do-over.
If you open it, you'll see.
Here we go.
It's closed.
Wait a minute. I'm pretty shocked.
What is this? I don't know.
Open it again.
What does that mean?
You know what I mean?
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
Okay, okay.
I have no idea.
That's Karin.
The one on the left.
Is this me?
Is this real?
Something's wrong, isn't it?
No, no, no.
That's not what I mean.
Look at the red one.
Remember the retro ones.
What? What? It's a start.
Is it the same?
I'm scared. Too scary.Scary. Too scary.
Crazy.
Is it similar?
More like this one.
It's not similar. I'm not surprised.
No, they don't. No, not at all.
Well, that's what I mean.
Do I look like him?
You're lying.
I'm just saying you probably look a little like this.
Can I eat it? Okay, then.
Can you eat it?
Don't be nervous.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous, too.
I don't know where to start.
Where do you want to eat?
Is it the omelet?
That's right.
There are so many different flavors of omelet. Speak for yourself.
It's a Tamura type flavor.
I want you to eat it.
I'd like to have a vegetable mother.
Vegetables.
Bon appétit.
I don't know.
It's beautiful.
I'm nervous.
Mmm.
Delicious?
Delicious!
I'm sweeter.
Much, much sweeter.
But it goes well with rice.
It's like a second helping.
Delicious!
Thank you very much
It's like a home-cooked meal!
I want you to go home and eat it all.
Can I take this home with me?
What? You're English.
What's this?
Stuffed meat.
This is really...
It's really good, isn't it?
Commercial.
I don't know, commercial's not the right word.
I don't know.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, it is.
Can we go?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
It's delicious. Really?
Yeah.
It's too nutritious.
Oh, it's hot.
It's good.
Not too much flavor?
Not too sweet.
Sweet.
Sweet?
Is this it?
I've never had this before.
It's delicious, even if you look at it with a critical eye.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm glad.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
But I think I like this best with fried eggs.
Thank you very much.
How do you like it? Are you going to work hard? What are your plans for the future?
No, I think I'll do my best.
I should have taken a picture of this.
I did. I'll give it to you.
You took it?
You can do your best with this.
Really?
Thank you for watching this far.
That's all for today's video.
If you are interested in eating my lunch
Please like and subscribe to my channel!
It was delicious!
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Did you recognize your face?
I didn't know it was my face.
I was scared.
Wait a minute.
Because, because, because.
I'm sorry I almost ate.
Scared, huh?
I'm so glad you did.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm glad.
undefined